[Music] I do
[Música]
n't know how to tell you these families I
no sé cómo deciros estos familias
don't know how to say this but well the
no sé cómo decir esto pero bueno lo
best thing was to
mejor era
tell you as quickly as possible okay
decirle lo más rápido posible vale
and
y
no the title doesn't write the title in the
no el título no escribe el título en el
clip you know that I don't usually I don't
clip ya sabéis que no acostumbro no
usually click bein and it's true I'm
acostumbro a hacer clic bein y es verdad
going to leave my main channel
yo voy a dejar mi canal principal
surely the secondary one also worth
seguramente el secundario también vale
in the ladies of course green the
en las señoras por supuesto verde la
lady not a chance very happy with my
señora ni de coña muy contenta con mi
lady no
señora no
but let's see
pero a ver
next week I have the
la semana que viene tengo el juego del
squid game surely I'll win and get rich
calamar seguramente gane y me haga rico
with that in fact today we're going to train
con eso de hecho hoy vamos a entrenar
Paulino today we're going to train hard so
paulino hoy vamos a entrenar duro así
between that next week I have
que entre que la semana que viene tengo
the squid game and I'm going to win and
el juego del calamar y voy a ganar y ya
with this I can retire
con esto me puedo retirar
well you don't have to retire because
bueno no se tienen por retirar porque la
half is washed remains tax but well I
mitad se lava queda hacienda pero bueno
won't pay tax I'll leave
no pagaré hacienda me iré
Veronica thank you thank you to whoever tweets
veronica gracias gracias a quien tweets
and you can subscribe okay
y os podéis suscribir vale
and apart from that I'm gaming more often
y aparte que soy gaming más seguido
Marta mark marked I'm still thinking
marta marca marcado yo pensando todavía
about the nationality has followed me mark
en la nacionalidad me ha seguido marca
gaming this is a sign that yes no I
gaming esto es señal de que ya sí no o
mean now I'm already a gamer I don't know if
sea ya ya soy gamer no sé si la semana
next week  well play there with with
que viene bien jugar yo allí con
ivai
con el ivai
with gres
con el gres
but nobody
pero nadie
knows realize that you guys I won't
sabe da cuenta de eso ustedes no me
shut up about that no that next week I'm going to
callo en eso no que la semana que viene
play with grefa let's
voy a jugar con grefa
see if you clicked javi not so much
a ver si has hecho clic javi no tanto
raul not so much as if
raúl no tanto
you left youtube my life will
como que dejaras youtube mi vida no
have no meaning
tendrá sentido
the life of a gamer jose sometimes it
la vida del gamer jose algunas veces te
leads you to decisions you know
lleva a decisiones sabe
still sometimes it leads you to decisions
aún a veces te lleva a decisiones
guys what
chavales
nonsense what nonsense just
vaya burradas vaya burrada lo que acaba
happened and it is that I come from the live of
de pasar y es que vengo del directo de
the lordship some of you have been in the
la señoría habéis estado algunos en el
live of the lordship today
directo de la señoría de hoy
the fart will get bigger but if how is it that you
el pedo se tirará más pero si como se
have a fart with me playing with
tiene un peo estando yo jugando con el
power every bad we are going to have
poder cada mala vamos a tener
how is it that you have a but playing the
como se tiene un pero jugando el huevo
squid egg next week we are going to
del calamar la semana que viene lo vamos
have it watch out because no don't do this to us we
a tener ojo porque no no nos hagas esto
love you you or your face of confusion
te queremos te o sur cara de confusión
totally I want the acne
totalmente quiero el acné
listen to me how to feel even worse
escúchame como sentir aún peor
or how the yaqui yells at me that
o como me grite el yaqui que la semana
next week in the tournament the least
que viene en el torneo los menos
important I think it will be if they
importantes yo creo que va a ser si se
played badly I think no no he since he is going to
jugaron mal creo no no él ya que me va
kill me
quiere matar
the spoiler the spoiler  he thinks p2 this one
el spoiler el spoiler él cree el p2 este
wants to kill me too who else is there
me quiere matar también quien más hay
some have confirmed that he will be there
han confirmado algunos que esté
some car his mother
algún coche su madre
some car his
algún coche su madre ha confirmado que
mother has confirmed that he will be there and now we see about Celine and from here yes yes I am confirming the tournament is 100% confirmed but some more neither him nor yes maybe I know more or less who is because we are in the group of
quién está porque estamos en el grupo de
records of course
discos claro
the team I think you are
el equipo creo que estás
the choco casita casita I
el choco casita casita
don't know who else is because in the group of
no sé quién es más porque en el grupo de
records there are more than 150 people so I do
discos hay más de 150 personas entonces
n't know who they are and who I don't
no sé quiénes son y quiénes no
imagine they have to take out the
me imagino que tienen que sacar a la
people that are left over it is not from here since he is
gente que sobra no es de aquí ya que me
going to yell at me right
va a gritar verdad
but with who to the team when I have to
pero con quien al equipo cuando tenga
play marbles who did
que jugar las canicas a quien buscó
Ricky look for is there
ricky está
but but but but
pero
god there is going to be revenge
pero pero pero dios va a haber venganza
against Díaz Ferrán do you think that when
contra díaz ferrán cree que cuando caiga
night falls they are not going to kill me
la noche no me van a matar
when night falls
cuando caiga la noche
to kill me even from several teams
para matarme incluso de varios equipos
true
verdad
but
pero
Paula we have to train a lot day I
paula tenemos que entrenar muchísimo día
mean but I have to
o sea pero yo tengo que
rethink that -he said-
yo repensar eso -dijo-
when it is that night to kill the
cuando sea la noche esa de matar la
rain has to carry a bomb even
lluvia tiene que llevar una bomba hasta
in the chest  I had
en el pecho
not fallen for the game at
no había caído en el juego de por la
night because then more or less the tartan
noche porque luego más o menos el tartán
axe
hacha
like the cakes to bastards
como las tartas a cabrones
style dead the one of 7
style dead el de 7
to these names that you do not see idea is
a estos nombres que no veis idea está
clear aha let's
claro
see the important thing is to participate also I
a ver lo importante es participar
can also negotiate
también puedo también podría negociar
also I could negotiate listen to me bros you did
también podría negociar escúchame bros
not kill me you come to my team
no me mataste vienes a mi equipo ya
we will see if it is sunk to see us
veremos si está hundido vernos
Kiko Rivera is there too
está kiko rivera también
but it is done
pero está hecho
your threat with cash Carl game over they will
tu amenaza con cash carl game over te
let you win it can be negotiated it can be
dejarán ganar se puede negociar
negotiated
se puede negociar
but using you know the list of
pero utilizando sabes la lista de
contestants
concursantes
I am looking forward to knowing the list of
estoy deseando saber la lista de
contestants man
concursantes tío
because they me in the record there are a
porque ellos yo en el disco están un
lot of people but of course in the record there are
montón de gente pero claro en el récord
in the group there are more than 150 and they are 150
hay en el grupo hay más de 150 y son 150
so we have to train powerful
así que tenemos que entrenar potentes
paulet especially the issue of the fights
paulet sobre todo el tema de las peleas
already the issue of jumps and that raises my
ya el tema de saltitos y eso me suben
balls a little
poco los [__]
thinking that we have to think
pensando que tenemos que pensar
what is there is already done here it is already
lo que hay ahí están ya está hecho acá
here it
está ya aquí
is serious we
está grave
should negotiate
deberíamos negociarse
I think that I think that they have
yo creo que yo creo que la que se han
thought about distributing the money if they kill me
pensado en repartir dinero si me matan a
is  clear
está clara
goodness I made a stripe to the choca
menos mal que le hice una raya al choca
it's true
es verdad
this nocturnal alpha
esta alfa
is what the roblón tournament and
son lo que lo del torneo de roblón y
some more many people have
algunos más muchas personas le han
put a price on your head crying face
puesto precio a tu cabeza cara llorando
and I don't blame him actually
y no le culpo en realidad
less searched
menos buscado
but look for the best channel just uploaded
pero busca el mejor canal acaba de subir
videos
vídeos
if you read the ceo don't watch salsa TV
si te lees al ceo no mirar tele salsero
this has been the live from orientals to the
este ha sido el directo de orientales al
ceo bars in the middle because average
ceo bares de todo el medio porque media
the name
el nombre
I want to feel your body next to mine
quiero sentir tu cuerpo junto al mío
because my
porque mi
name
nombre
directly he is to the ceo an average of
directamente él es al ceo una media de
7,200 viewers
7.200 espectadores
an average
una media
with a peak of almost 12,000
con un pico de casi 12.000
with a peak
con un pico
refers to pulsar they had uploaded the
se refiere a pulsar se habían subido la
reaction that they don't want you to see what
reacción que no quieren que veas
how what the
cómo
[ __ ] did he throw himself
qué [__] se echó tiro
what the [ __ ] have you done I
qué [__] has hecho
mean really what the [ __ ] is that
o sea realmente qué [__] es eso
ask vegeta to get you the
pídele a vegeta que te entren los a
stripes
rayas
I have to train hard okay but right now
tengo que entrenar duro vale pero ahora
we are in something serious I mean
mismo estamos en algo serio o sea
my face can't be on the internet
mi cara no puede estar en internet al
next to a dog to jacket
lado un perro a chaqueta
we are talking about that my face
estamos hablando de que mi cara ahora
right now is exposed on the internet
mismo está expuesta en internet
laughing so normal next to a dog
riéndome tan normal al lado de un perro
against the jacket
contra el chaqueta
fine dog signs but dog final for
perro fino señales pero perro final para
a fine dog no
un perro fino no
pacino welcome
pacino bienvenido
I love it because the intro as serious not
me encanta porque la intro como seria no
the intro as very serious
la intro como muy seria
that the alpha light
que la luz alfa
look
fíjate
what you get here when you put the
lo que te sale aquí cuando pones la
[ __ ] of these channels of plus salsa
[__] de estas de canales de plus salsa
salsas a garbage channel do not subscribe
salsas una basura del canal no suscriba
and okay
y vale
and here you get this salsa to dance
y te sale aquí esto salsa para bailar
you decide if we say goodbye or not it
ustedes decidir si nos despedimos o no
is knowing that this channel is really
es saber que este canal en verdad es
to get rid of the agents
para quitarse los agentes
eliminate the end but not the series of
elimina el final pero no el serie de
this channel is to take away your mind
este canal es para quitarse la mente
next to mine because my
junto al mío porque mi
name does not want to
nombre no quiere
hear me paulo really and I tell you
escucharme paulo de verdad y te lo digo
here
aquí
is all the lordship of witness right now
está toda la señoría de testigo ahora
is that if more of the lordship the
mismo es que si más de la señoría el
video is that I have stolen from the lordship
vídeo sea que he robado de la señoría
on top of everything
encima de todo
how crazy that today many people become
qué locura que hoy mucha gente se haga
members with a tutorial and show me that it
miembro con tutorial y me demuestre que
works because I believe that this one I believe
funciona porque yo creo que ese yo creo
that this tutorial does not work
que este tutorial no funciona
[Music]
a
why did you want to look at the end paul
para que quería que mirar al final paul
doolin welcome to the king so that he stops
doolin bienvenido al rey para que deje
seeing the car
de ver al auto
[Music]
[Música]
I mean this is touching the [ __ ] no I
o sea esto es tocar la [__] no
mean this is already
o sea esto ya es el
deciding to welcome the queen
decidir a dar la bienvenida a la reina
this is already saying it is
esto ya es el decir
not  that doesn't fit that the shots from
no es que no cuadre que los tiros de
far away like your teeth before putting on
lejos como tus dientes antes de ponerte
the braces
el aparato
like your teeth to me that no to me my
como los dientes a mí que no a mí no me
teeth didn't come out they threw it out of the
salieron los dientes me lo tiraron del
barn my mouth was a
granero tenía la boca que era un
maze
laberinto
and you find it funny made paulo or something
y te parece gracioso hecho paulo o algo
sabrok cold of you in the shitty brat
sabrok fría de tu en el niñato de [__]
look at the shitty brat what he does he takes
fíjate el niñato de [__] lo que hace
refuge the [ __ ]
se acoge el [__]
makes a tutorial for the lady telling
hace un tutorial para la señora diciendo
the ladies with chitu mother we are if
a las señoras con chitu madre estamos si
those don't emerge at the cheapest
esas no surgimos al más barato
okay
vale
I react he doesn't upload
yo reacciono él no sube
and he starts moving the icons so they don't
y se pone a mover los iconos para que no
fit because of the balls and now take it
cuadren debido a los huevos y ahora coge
and being live I stop the
y estando yo en directo me para mí el
chat saying look look in the end look what I've
chat diciendo mira mira al final mira lo
done but what I've done because
que he hecho pero lo que he hecho porque
these [ __ ] did
ha hecho estos [__]
and c I do
y c
n't know
no sé
he feels
él se siente
funny or something look look what I've
gracioso o algo mira mira lo que he
done he flexes a muscle but at the table
hecho me saca un músculo pero a la mesa
this thumbnail
esta miniatura
I had watch the chicken video on
yo había ve el vídeo del pollo de
youtube okay whatever I'm going to
youtube vale lo que me vaya que voy a
abandon my main bed is that I'm going to
abandonar mi cama principal es que voy a
abandon this channel 9 thousand 170 people
abandonar este canal 9 mil 170 personas
oh my god  rude old man I
oh my god grosero el viejito
mean here come the [ __ ] to
o sea aquí vienen los [__] a
comment nonsense about me not this
comentar tonterías sobre mí no este
channel not
canal no
javi well son I'm talking about has a video
javi bien hijo hablo de tiene un vídeo
on his secondary channel
en su canal secundario
730 let's see
730 a ver
and what is the secondary channel
y cuál es el canal secundario
everyone I'm a doctor
a todos soy médico
you're subscribed for nothing
estás suscrito al pedo
must be the editor of the main channel
debe ser el editor del canal principal
what I was
que estaba
I was thinking precisely for
estaba pensando yo eso precisamente para
the video that meditated the other day of the
el vídeo que medito el otro día del
main channel
canal principal
at minute 27 30
en el minuto 27 30
cloud blow
cloud blow
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
luckily not the exit well guys
por suerte no la salida bien chicos por
luckily the exit quite bad everything
suerte la salida bastante mal todo
the kid didn't follow me on twitter
no me siguió el chaval en twitter
[Music]
[Música]
on this guy's secondary channel
en el canal secundario de este pavo
okay no there
vale no
are no videos that are like that there are no videos
no hay ningún vídeo que sean así
that are like that
no hay ningún vídeo que sea así
the kid followed me on twitter and thanked me
me siguió el chaval en twitter y me dio
and everything
las gracias y demás
for the video I'm going to start wife
por el vídeo voy a empezar a wife
[ __ ] but saw the reaction when nobody
[__] pero vio la reacción al nadie
uploaded read
subir leyó
what do you think of controversial youtubers
qué opinas de los youtubers de polémicas
like javier la beira or bad well the
como javier la beira o mal pues en
truth is I entertain myself quite a bit sometimes
verdad yo me entretengo bastante a veces
well it's been a long time since I
bueno os hace mucho que no le voy a
downloaded it and oliveira but well it's a
bajar y oliveira pero bueno es un
Spanish youtube that basically like  that
youtube español que básicamente como que
keeps you informed not of the world I would have to
te mantiene informado no del mundo yo
see what moves happen but I don't
tuviera a ver qué movidas pasan pero no
know I don't like
sé no me gusta el contenido me da un
the content I don't like what happens to me very well the gentleman s not long ago I saw him how well I remembered that gentleman on youtube stopped recommending that channel to me youtube stopped recommending that channel to me in this video from September it cools off I stopped they mention me in a video with one
detuve me mencionan en un vídeo de un
million three hundred thousand views god
millón trescientas mil visitas dios
lord it's true he told me sir the
señor es verdad me ha dicho señor
gentleman I'm going to start with this now I
el señor voy a empezar con esto ya
suppose because of course worrying me
supongo porque claro preocupándome yo
worrying because a kid who
preocupándome por que un chaval que el
says that he really likes me who does
que dice que yo le caigo muy bien
n't care about what
que no le importa lo que suba de
content I upload but he watches me because he
contenido sino que me ve a mí porque le
really likes me
caigo muy bien
saying that youtube stopped
diciendo que youtube dejo de
recommending my channel of course so you can
recomendarle a mi canal claro para que
see that the channel youtube has stopped
veáis que el canal youtube lo ha dejado
recommending it
de recomendar
and of course there is no one who called me the
y claro no hay un que me ha llamado el
gentleman no matter how many
señor
colorful sweatshirts they
por más sudadera de colores que me
put on me god
pongan dios
because it doesn't matter I don't have
por da igual no
it screwed screwed already in the
lo tengo [__] [__] ya
end what did grandpa have google mom that
final que tuvo el abuelo google mamá que
next week
la semana que viene
I will there the load assured gave
yo ahí la carga aseguró dio
Joel Abaca assured  well there's going to be
joel abacá aseguró bueno va a haber
chicken
pollo
18 minutes before starting with the
18 minutos antes de empezar con el tema
beat topic of the extract appears 18 little
del beat del extracto comparece 18
minutes fine signs fine
minutitos finos señales
fine sure he was generous with the
fino fino seguro fue generoso con lo del
gentleman here Yolanda can drive to
señor acá yolanda puede manejar a
places please can you shoot him
lugares porfa puedes balearlo
from one ask one day
de un pide un día
give him a chance a few months
le da una oportunidad unos meses
marked main eyes because it makes me feel
marcaban principal ojos porque me da
sorry
pena
but I think the law mixing the
pero yo creo que la ley mezclando los
contents but it is what there is you
contenidos pero es que es lo que hay
knew I will continue making the
sabias voy a seguir haciendo el
content that I make and if I did this
contenido que hago y si hice este
live crying not in a way as if
directo lloriqueando no en plan como si
I were abandoning girlfriend of encouragement a
fuera yo abandona novia de ánimo un
channel really for it always
canal en verdad para ello siempre
in the end what matters to me is the
al final lo que me importa es el
I care about everything I would like it to have
me importa todo me gustaría que tuviera
the visits it deserves
las visitas que merece
sincerely that I know that I know that
sinceramente que yo sé que yo sé que ese
channel deserves many more visits
canal merece muchas más visitas
but does not recommend them I had that channel well
pero no los recomienda yo tuve ese canal
it does not recommend it I believe for the
pues no lo recomienda yo creo por la
mind I believe that there are several factors
mente yo creo que hay varios factores
as I have already explained
como ya he explicado
the factor that the factor that you upload
el factor de que el factor de que subes
content for two types two or three
contenido para dos tipos dos o tres
different types of public then in
tipos de público diferente entonces en
a video I recommend it to you
un vídeo te lo recomiendo
in the end they are killing the channel no but they
al final van matando el canal no pero
are videos that are a trip it matters if they are
son vídeos que son viaje interesa si son
good no but well there are several things
buenos no pero bueno hay varias cosas
for which  then apart
por las que por las que dan luego aparte
from the fact that YouTube has to stop recommending
de que youtube haya dejar de recomendar
that channel
ese canal
[Music]
[Música]
because that guy for example
porque ese tío por ejemplo
videos of this from the Costa Rican news are
vídeos de esto del noticiero ticos están
stagnating super cool and the processed
estancando súper chulos y los tramitados
the site super cool man but what if
el sitio súper guay tío pero y ver si
doing them in the end what matters to me
haciéndolos al final lo que me importa
is the final salary of the month and the
es el sueldo final del mes y el sueldo
final salary of the month still fits me okay
final del mes todavía me cuadra vale
then I don't care I keep working
entonces me da igual yo sigo trabajando
all day ping ping ping ping ping
todo el día ping ping ping ping ping
ping yes it is true that topics for
ping sí que es verdad que temas por
example these two videos
ejemplo estos dos vídeos
these two videos I was making the
estos dos vídeos estaba haciendo los
days
días
these two videos pulled from research newspaper archives
estos dos vídeos tirado de hemeroteca de
becoming save me since
investigación volviéndome sálvame desde
the year 2013
el año 2013
complete here browsing a click here
completos aquí recorriendo un clic aquí
and now and these videos I have enjoyed god it
y ya y estos vídeos he disfrutado dios
is not that I do not like the topic of the
no es que no me gusten los tema de la
youth of course there are topics of the
chavalería por supuesto hay temas de la
youth that I love to know but it is
chavalería que me encantan saber pero es
that the topics that I really like about the
que los temas que realmente me gustan de
youth right now are turned off
la chavalería ahora mismo están apagados
now the topic of the youth many
ahora los tema de la chavalería muchas
little things about this one kill me in the
cositas de este me matan en el
video game the other one gets hooked on the
videojuego el otro se engancha con el
other one the video game and like no  look at me
otro el videojuego y como que no me mira
for example this topic this yes this
por ejemplo este tema esto sí que este
is the other bad one the fight at the aurum
es el otro mal la pelea de aurum
convention and in fact those topics do
convention y y de hecho esos temas si
have views
tienen visitas
and I also like to know the topics for
y también a mí también son los temas por
example this video I really like to let you
ejemplo este vídeo me gusta mucho
know what I don't like
hacerlo saber a mí lo que no me gustan
for example a lot what doesn't catch my
por ejemplo mucho lo que no me llama la
attention a lot are topics type
atención mucho son temas tipos
by type or I don't know who kills me in
por tipo o no sé quién me mata en
tortilla the house explodes you know but the
tortilla la explota la casa sabe pero lo
rest cool but well I'm going to keep
demás guay pero bueno yo voy a seguir
doing all all all it would be that the
haciendo todos todos todos sería que los
topics are weaker you know such 10,000 today
temas son más flojos sabe tal 10.000 hoy
we were on the signal Doctor Strange would go
éramos en la señal iría doctor extraño
12 thousand there was a peak of 12,000
12 mil ha habido un pico de 12.000
viewers today in the live on TV
espectadores hoy en el directo en teles
to the pse I hate that channel vaquita Telecinco
al pse odio ese canal vaquita telecinco
in the media I only warned you already this channel is going to
en medios sólo os lo avisó ya este canal
remove Telecinco in the middle
va a quitar a telecinco en medio
but it hasn't been only therefore
pero es que no ha sido solo por lo tanto
from today it's that the channel is getting more and more it's that
de hoy es que cada vez el canal va más
the channel is getting more and more each
es que cada vez el canal va a más cada
time they like the live shows more and more that maybe
vez le gustan más los directos de más
the director catch me I
que a lo mejor el director me cojo me
start talking about any of
pongo a hablar de cualquier chorrada de
my nonsense and no  it goes away so it's
las mías y no se va
not just to
o sea que no está solamente para
listen to the controller theme although it's
escuchar el tema del controlador aunque
not going away 12,000 spectators we had
no se va 12.000 espectadores teníamos
families today
hoy familias
twelve thousand peak spectators it's for
doce mil espectadores de pico es durante
a while here
un rato aquí
and then it started going down to here this
y ya luego fue bajando hasta aquí esto
is this drop because people send
es esta bajada porque manda la gente
direct pairs of talisman okay but
pares directos de talismán vale pero ya
then it remained here we were
luego se mantuvo aquí que estuvimos
talking about 67 thousand spectators or rather
hablando de 67 mil espectadores o sea
but the previous days the previous days have
pero es que los días anteriores los días
also been the most watched live
también ha sido el directo más más visto
ah well thanks to the anonymous person
ah pues gracias a la persona anónima
thanks to the anonymous person who
gracias a la persona anónima que me
just sent me for me it's 20 turkey okay
acaba de mandar por mí son 20 pavo vale
remember that you have vision in case you
recordar que tenéis visión por si
want to collaborate by vision in case there are no
queréis colaborar por visón por si no
super char verse at 685 18 2
hay de los súper char verse a 685 18 2
954 okay but now incredible incredible
954 vale pero ahora increíble increíble
incredible it doesn't matter I keep working
increíble da igual yo sigo trabajando
everything in all day that I don't like it's
todo en todo el día que no me guste pues
not worth something okay for the moment I have a
no vale algo vale por el momento me lo
good time and the salary at the end of my
paso bien y el sueldo al final de mi
block is worth
cuadra vale
tournament week because I'm short on
semana del torneo porque ya me falta
time in the day I'm going to have to leave a
tiempo en el día voy a tener que dejar
lot of things aside next week
muchas cosas de lado la semana que viene
to participate in the tournament
para participar en el torneo
and if the main house doesn't wake up
y si no espabila en casa principal
man i'm going to convert posters being
hombre voy a convertir carteles al ser
one of the strong and skilled
uno de los fuertes y hábiles
the strong channels now if this is a
los canales fuertes ahora si esto es una
possibility if it ends up dying the
posibilidad si termina muriendo ya el
main channel but I already tell you or
canal principal pero es que ya os digo o
rather since I was talking about this with
sea ya que esto lo estuve hablando con
them in the live of charismas and
ellos en el directo de carismas y de
enrique subscribe to their channels I was not seriously
enrique suscribiros a sus canales no
talking about this with them there
estuve sería hablando esto con ellos ahí
in their live and precisely the
en su directo y precisamente al día
next day he uploaded a video to
siguiente subió un video a
javi oliveira the main channel that
javi oliveira el canal principal que me
blew me away
que me reventó
that it was made it
que fue hecha
already has almost 70 thousand views and has 12
tiene ya casi 70 mil visitas y tiene 12
thousand likes you know what happens with
mil like sabéis que lo que pasa con los
videos of this theme of gossip
vídeos de esta temática de los cotilleos
on TV and that it doesn't die in you or
de la tele y eso que no muere en ti o
the salsa of the youtubers the
los salseros de los youtubers lo que el
problem is that maybe you get more
problema es que a lo mejor te coge más
views the first days or the first
visitas los primeros días o el primer
day
día
but the week ends most of them there are
pero se acaba la semana la mayoría hay
some that don't but most of them end but but the
algunos que no pero la mayoría se acaban
subject of TV all
pero pero el tema de la tele toda la
life keeps running visiting there are still
vida sigue corriendo de visita hay
videos of the sea it's only
vídeos todavía de mar sólo me está
running me I feel still
corriendo me siento todavía
then in the end well look what I said that I
entonces al final pues fíjate que dije
said that is in this live I was
dije eso es en este directo estuve
saying this and the next day  I uploaded
diciendo esto y al día siguiente subí
this video repetto then at night we
este vídeo repetto luego por la noche
upload these news that well
subimos estas noticias que bueno
as long as it gets 25 or 30 thousand views it
mientras que coja 25 o 30 mil visitas me
works for me although I think they should get
sirve aunque yo creo que deberían [__]
at least 40 or 50 thousand
mínimo 40 50 mil
but well it is still
pero bueno
because I think that these
sigue siéndolo porque yo creo que estos
videos I think that some of the monitors
vídeos yo creo que algunos de monitores
exhibitions one that one bursts I am going
exposiciones uno que uno reviente ya voy
to get into a niche there well also
a meterme ahí en un nicho bueno además
what happens is the news
lo que pasa tiene los noticieros todo el
everyone is putting very positive comments
mundo está poniendo comentarios muy
and many likes you
y muchos like
understand so I am going to continue
me entendéis entonces lo voy a seguir
doing okay what I am doing but
haciendo vale lo que estoy haciendo pero
'guaje' dude very cool the truth is that
'guaje' tío muy guay la verdad que
wait to hear this uploaded that
espera oír subido este que visitas
real views has forty something thousand seven
reales tiene cuarenta y tantas mil siete
thousand like these videos have a
mil like estos vídeo tienen un cpm
pretty high cpm you know because they are from Spain
bastante alto sabes porque son de españa
and well well well I would like it to
y bien bien bien a mí me gustaría que
have more truth in the subject of the
tuviera más la verdad el tema de los
news and some of the pse or the
noticieros y algunos al pse o de los
kids but yes it is true that
chavales pero sí que es verdad que es
the topics of the topics that
que los temas de los temas que a
we like here people were already
nosotros nos gustan aquí la gente ya
subscribed here are topics of hunger
estaba aquí suscrita son temas de hambre
for example the other day from the iac ingrid
por ejemplo del otro día del iac ingrid
adolfo labores or if it is well or when
adolfo labores o si está bien o cuando
the  dallas trials when they
lleguen los juicios de dallas cuando
come no no I'm going to convert the
lleguen no no voy a convertir canal
dollar channel and watch continue uploading to the
dólar y ver seguir subiendo al canal
main channel the two topics well investigate
principal los dos temas bien investigar
and everything well edit and all the videos
y todo bien editar y todos los vídeos
that are worth the penalties well like this one that
que merezcan las penas bien como éste
uploaded today the video that uploaded today is
que subió hoy el vídeo que subió hoy es
a [ __ ] gem
una [__] joya
although we are interested in the lordship this
aunque nos interese la señoría este
video is a gem 40 minutes of that
vídeo es una joya 40 minutos de esa
song
canción
when the trials of the trials
cuando vengan los juicios de los juicios
of evil come to the trials of
del mal a los juicios de
others youtube I
otros youtube
don't know what that you
no sé qué
already know that the channel that is going to
eso ya sabéis que el canal que lo va a
report it well is going to be this one the
informar bien va a ser éste
shortest
a los más cortos
these topics are the good ones but they don't come out
estos temas son los buenos pero no salen
every day we
todos los días
have a streak of topics
que llevamos una racha de temas
at the ceiling if those topics do very well
en el techo si le va muy bien esos temas
but it's that apart from the fact that I don't
pero es que a mí aparte de que no me
like them that much my audience doesn't
gustan tanto tampoco a mi público le
like
gusta tanto
the news that much but that is not the
a godoy la noticia pero que no es lo
same as a good being followed by wii
mismo que un buen ser seguido de wii
lying or a good bug blaming
mintiendo o buen [__] echándole en cara
someone for something they have done or the
a alguien algo que haya hecho o las
old girlfriends trying to cancel it
novias de edad la intentando cancelarlo
and dismantle the engine statement because everything
y desmonta motor comunicado porque todo
lies
mentira
reigns thank you very much damn it's almost almost
reina muchas gracias [__] casi es casi
two years
dos años
Joan's little issue  flat joan flat off it's
los temita de joan plana joan plana off
getting boring the last ones
ya llega a aburrir los últimos
lately it's been talked about again
últimamente se ha hablado otra vez
answered already so that it does
contestó ya para que
n't take anything
no tome nada
when when the trial comes that's going to
cuando cuando llegue el juicio eso va a
be good when the trial
ser bueno cuando el juicio
but well happy in not believing that I
pero bueno contento en no creer que
'm disappointed by the channels or
estoy desilusionado por los canales ni
much less because I think I'm in the
mucho menos porque creo que estoy en los
best moments to see if I can
mejores momentos a ver
find a fault the CPM for January is
por poner alguna pega el cpm de enero es
very low
muy bajo
the CPM for January is a little disgusting god we
el cpm de enero da un poco de asco dios
both do live extracts of
los dos hago directos extractos de
live shows on TV when it's news but
directos en teles al ser noticia pero
this is said here an
esto se dice aquí una posibilidad
exemplary possibility that if the main channel
ejemplar que si el canal principal
died and I told him look listen to me that it tires me
muriese y le dije la mira escúchame que
that I don't make more edited videos
me cansa que no hago más vídeos editados
that he
que lo
knows
sabe
or whatever I would do
o lo que sea yo haría
javier canijo or luck both subscribe
javier canijo o la surte ambos suscriban
to javi's main channel it's called plus
al canal principal de javi se llama plus
salsa well turbo plan I leave you to god
salsa bueno turbo plan te dejo a dios
luck in your live show that welcomes that here I
suerte en tu directo que acoge que aquí
also have to put up with radio this is what
tengo que aguantar también radio es lo
happens
que pasa
that
que
if one day the main channel really touches my
si algún día el canal principal me toca
dick and that's it that war
mucho la [__] y ya es que esa guerra ya
since many of us are going to upload the video the
que muchas estamos a subir el vídeo el
same topic on the secondary one on the
mismo tema en el secundario en el
main one bird and throw images of the
principal ave y tira imágenes del
secondary because I think the
secundario porque es que yo creo que el
main channel
canal principal
is a little screwed in terms of positioning
está un poco [__] de posicionamiento
but oh well if one day it's my turn then I'll
pero bueno si algún día me tocará pues
do the live shows of kids,
haré los directos de chavalería
the songs that I like, edited,
los temas que me gusta editados los
accredited, but I'll upload them to Xavi the
acreditados pero lo subiré a xavi el
Canine too and the
canino también y de los temas de
TV songs on TV to the PSE, that is, live, it's
televisión en teles al pse o sea directo
been edited, be it news because to be a pain, I have to
se ha editado sea noticia que para [__]
put up with this [ __ ]
es que tengo que aguantar estas [__]
here on kids it has, I don't feel like it, I'm
aquí en chavalería tiene no me da la
already 36 years old,
gana tengo ya 36 años
thousand viewers, I come from having 12
mil espectadores yo vengo de tener 12
thousand on TV, cleanliness,
mil en teles aseo
[ __ ] madness, 12 thousand and I have 12 thousand
[__] locura 12 miles y yo 12 mil
viewers,
espectadores
put it in the dark, I do
put al oscurísima
n't feel like it, be an edited video,
no me apetezca sea un vídeo editado
profile today for seven songs,
perfil ya hoy por siete temas
being from YouTube to see,
al ser de youtube para ver camino
edited path too and look there I'm
editado también y fíjate ahí estoy
talking about video, look at you what
hablando de vídeo fíjate tú lo que lo
takes hours on the two videos
que tarda horas en los dos vídeos estos
here and I'm talking about that video from the
acá y estoy hablando de ese vídeo del
bid edited from the main channel and I
bid edita del canal principal y lo
study it this morning in the second
estudio hoy por la mañana en la segunda
part look at the work that I've left
parte fíjate el trabajo que he dejado
a relic
una reliquia
these days for a reason I live surrounded by
estos días por un motivo vivo rodeada de
this problem where  it seems that a channel
este problema donde al parecer un canal
no longer works as before, that of
ya no funciona como antes eso del
motivating youtubers and as they have other
motivar youtuber y como tiene otras
options, well, look, they prefer to take advantage of
opciones pues mira prefiere aprovechar
giving themselves a place to insist with,
darse un lugar de insistir con de
clearly they have no results and there may be
claramente no tiene resultados y puede
several reasons that lead to said
haber varios motivos que lleven a dicho
dynamic, for example,
dinámico por ejemplo
I think that canary has never, ever liked me
yo creo que ese canario nunca nunca me
[Music]
ha gustado
the videos as they are tiber is that it does not
los vídeos como son tiber es que a mí no
fit me that the videos that I upload are no longer
me cuadra que los vídeos que yo subo
interesting not a chance they are not
cañas deja de interesar ni de coña no se
recommended and their calls you know that I
recomiende y sus llamadas ya sabéis que
try to contribute as much as possible or
ir intento aportar lo máximo posible o
main video and the secondary when it
vídeo principal y el secundario cuando
was the debate with turbo site at 10,000
fue el debate con turbo sitio a 10.000
viewers there
espectadores
were 10,000 viewers I have had them
había 10.000 espectadores los he tenido
many times
muchas veces
several times the debate with Jackie
varias el debate con jackie
of having many times 10,000
de tener muchas veces 10.000
viewers
espectadores
so I really think that the
así que de verdad que creo que el canal
tele sal channel is going to blow up very hard it is going to
tele sal se os va a reventar muy fuerte
be very crazy
va a ser muy loco
I see your videos in the secondary and I do not
yo veo tus vídeos en el secundario y no
see them in the main one because the topic
los veo en el principal porque el tema
is repeated and this happens to many that is why
se repite y esto les pasa a muchos por
the main one does not work
eso el principal no tira
that I for example there are topics I
que yo por ejemplo hay temas yo
[Music]
[Música]
of the edited
de los editados
topic
tema
listen to me
escúchame
[Music]
[Música]
well almost everyone almost everyone
bueno casi todos casi todos
the meta game fight tries people
la pelea de meta game intenta gente
the lode
la lode
[Music]
[Música]
the other day I see this to
lo del otro día yo esto lo veo para
park secondary or what am I going to
aparcar secundarios o sea para que voy a
take and this and I'm going to record it
[__] y esto y lo voy a lo voy a grabar
and I'm going to send it to him success so he can
y se lo voy a mandar éxito para que lo
edit it these are things that we see
edite yo estos son cosas que las vemos
for a secondary channel
para canal secundario
or in other words to talk about it live rationally
o sea para hablarlo en directo racional
roll up stockings and with the padding and
enrollar medias y con el relleno y
upload them give I don't see it for a video
subirlos dar no lo veo para un vídeo
for the main channel honestly
para el canal principal sinceramente
or
o
is it punished from the
está castigado de las analíticas de
size analytics where the
tamaño de dónde vienen las visitas
guided tours and notifications come from maybe it
guiadas y de notificaciones a lo mejor
comes to them in 1500 2000 totally
les viene en 1500 2000 totalmente
[Music]
[Música]
one of the last videos kids that
uno de los últimos vídeos chavalería que
was very good the one of the wine river
fue muy bien el del río wine
has 90 thousand views
tiene 90 mil visitas
and that one has ninety thousand seven months in
y ese tiene noventa mil siete meses en
the statistics and it shows you that due to
las estadísticas y te marca que por
notifications your followers two thousand
notificaciones seguidores tuyos dos mil
and something people have seen the video the
y pico de personas visto el vídeo el
rest have been through searches
resto han sido por búsquedas
[ __ ] on my channel it is hidden visit
[__] en mi canal está escondido visita
sometimes the question that this generates is
a veces la pregunta que esto genera es
being punished or is it that they are no longer
de ser castigados o es que ya no
interested well I'm going to give you  my
interesan bien yo os voy a dar mi
opinion based on my experience but not
opinión en base a mi experiencia pero no
as a content creator but as a
como creadora de contenido sino como
consumer of this name since the
consumidora de este nombre desde el
video of the unions photos of this
vídeo de los sindicatos fotos de esto
that I was looking for my video to get
que estaba buscando mi vídeo para sacar
the invoice and how the youtube chicken
la facturita y como el pollo de youtube
defeats the union youtubers riojana
derrota al sindicato youtubers riojana
in the canaries but as with god
en canarias pero como con dios pollo de
youtube chicken it's going to be hopefully a
youtube va a ser ojalá que se haga un
video is made I'm
vídeo
going back too low
voy atrás demasiado baja
laziness big and big
la pereza grande y grande
if I have dreams lides lemonade
si tengo sueños lides limonada
but I already tell you lemonade again
pero ya te digo limonada de nuevo
awake since 9
despierto desde las 9
[Music]
[Música]
but we have to train now we
pero hay que entrenar ahora
have to train now when we see the
hay que entrenar ahora cuando veamos al
ceo
ceo
[Music]
[Música]
the chicken that I'm watching
el pollo que estoy viendo
that I'm watching
que estoy viendo
[Music]
[Música]
or rather the next one
o sea que el siguiente
if just waste a lot of time
si solo perder bastante tiempo
welcome to manuel I would swear that it has to me
bienvenido a manuel juraría que me tiene
in the same way that there are channels
que de la misma forma que hay canales
that upload videos every day and don't
que suben vídeos todos los días y no
work there are others in which they upload
funcionan hay otros en los cuales suben
one a month and they keep starting it which
uno al mes y lo sigue empezando lo que
gives me a certain impression of the
me genera cierta impresión de en el
interest you have in a channel or maybe it
interés que tienes en un canal o tal vez
may be higher than the amount that is
es puede ser superior a la cantidad que
uploaded and youtube doesn't punish it because it is
sube y youtube no lo castiga porque de
enough if the people who upload the
sobra si la gente que sube el vídeo
monthly video would be because Castilla dictated another
mensual estaría pues castilla dictó otro
please don't leave me without my nights of
por favor no me dejes sin mis noches de
salt or face crying loud
sal se o cara llorando fuerte corazón
broken heart I will think about it
roto me lo pensaré
crying but of course in this video
llorando pero claro en este vídeo
arm wrestling in the as an example because it is
pulseada en la como ejemplo porque es
a youtuber willy agreed increase
una youtuber willy convenido aumente
has to the extreme good which although
tiene hasta el extremo bueno cual aunque
youtube did not notify me of their videos
youtube no me notificara de sus vídeos
from time to time I had to overcome to
de vez en cuando me tocó superar para
see has been uploaded angle
ver se ha subido ángulo
I imagine that it would not be within the
imagino que no sería dentro del universo
variable universe of the same other personal I assume
variable de lo mismo otro personal asumo
again that youtube would never give
de nuevo que youtube él nunca se daría
that channel because it was to be of not stop
ese canal porque era ser de no para de
searching or to meet him to put it
buscar o de encontrarse con él a meter
is for my reason others because they
es por el motivo mío otras porque
want to see old videos etcetera
quieren ver vídeos antiguos etcétera
etcetera etcetera but as I was saying
etcétera etcétera pero como os decía
this is already an established channel for many
éste ya es un canal establecido muchos
years I do
años
not understand why youtube takes away my
no entiendo por qué youtube me quita la
membership
membresía
because it takes it away because it does not have it to
pues se la quita porque no lo tiene para
renew automatically
que se renueve automáticamente
being a movie it is much easier for
al ser de película es bastante más fácil
you to eat it whole not with desire of
que te lo comas entero no con ganas de
javi this is the show you
javi este es el show
need current things then my
necesitas cosas actuales entonces mi
head wake up and memories has passed
cabeza espabilar y recuerdos ha pasado
a duty of salt was created in 2019 that
un deber de sal se ha creado en 2019 que
literally does not  has affected but
literalmente no ha afectado pero que
now
ahora
that is a girl in the guy but
eso sí que es chica en la al tío pero
there are two or three channels like that of people from
hay dos o tres canales así de gente de
Latin America
latinoamérica
like that channels that the videos say you well I had
así canales que los vídeos dice tú bueno
the arms
tuve los brazos
video let's go super simple nine minutes
vídeo vamos súper sencillo nueve minutos
eight minutes a few videos very few
ocho minutos unos vídeos muy pocos
videos a video every week or every gas and
vídeos un vídeo cada semana o cada gas y
also the videos with a million two million
tb los vídeos con un millón dos millones
the worst mistake of greg 1 with 3 1 with 3
el peor error de greg 1 con 3 1 con 3
million and screwed but if to see the
millones y [__] pero si a ver los
videos well they are not
vídeos bien no son
to our asset because the desire and the
a nuestro activo porque el deseo y los
reasons but
motivos pero
congratulations on this channel here
felicidades por este canal de aquí
called pato hornea where very smart
llamados pato hornea donde muy listillo
applied the drill strategy so that the
aplicó la estrategia de drill para que
heritage sleeps minecraft that
los el patrimonio duerme minecraft que
literally made some other video
literalmente hacía algún que otro vídeo
another one seeming like a new game with
otro pareciendo un juego nuevo con
sent by lucas regretted things and
enviados por lucas lamentó cosas y
coherent nothing but
coherente nada pero
[Music]
[Música]
with the series he made in which friends
con la serie que hizo en la cual amigos
of his, well look, they chase him between 6 he
suyos pues mira le persiguen entre 6
tries to pass the game yes it is incredible
intenta pasar el juego sí es increíble
because it is also another
porque además es otra
but some videos of the main one are
pero algunos vídeos del principal son
summarized from the secondary although edited you do not
resumidos del secundario aunque editados
want to see them simply do not repeat
no apetece verlos simplemente no repitas
content many greetings
contenido muchos saludos
but
pero
as that is
como
how you are going to be after
así vas a ser tú después del
training Xavi
entrenamiento xavi
I have my doubts Paulo  I
tengo mis dudas paulo
have my question Paulo
tengo mi duda paulo
for a company to have dreams or Carme
para una empresa tener sueños o carme
everything and went from 0 to this that I experience
todo y pasó de 0 a esto que experimento
on the screen was much better no I
en pantallita era mucho mejor no no me
'm not straying because apart from the
estoy desviando porque aparte de la
series as I have been doing to super
series como he estado haciendo a súper
known did other things like
conocido hizo otras cosas tipo quedaron
his friend was left out and although he puts himself in
fuera su amigo y aunque se pone en
situations in Minecraft the rest of
situaciones en el minecraft el resto de
humanity gives us laziness and he stressed that he
la humanidad nos da pereza y recalcó que
already had the boom now those videos were
ya tenía el boom ahora esos vídeos lo
devastating him also that he made short take
arrasaban también que hizo corto
advantage of the opportunity when this I do not
aprovechar la oportunidad cuando esto no
mean that there have been copies and
quiero decir que haya habido copias y
pastes or for fun or whatever you are
pegas o por diversión o lo que se os
paid because it is the little head simply
pague porque es la cabecita simplemente
are examples of signs that out of nowhere have
son ejemplos de señas que de la nada han
stood out in a very very short period of time
resaltado en un periodo de tiempo muy
and far from ending where they
muy corto y lejos de acabar donde
started and that will end their boom
empezaron y que se terminarán su boom
they have known how to take advantage of things
han sabido aprovechar las cosas
spectacularly to put something similar
espectacularmente por poner algo similar
and of the time of age we could talk
y de la época de edad podríamos hablar
about that the beginning was called
de que el principio se llamó así
this
este
at the beginning
al principio
in fact
de hecho
which is not relevant the issue is that
lo cual no es relevante el tema es que
as you can see it has a large
como podéis apreciar posee una gran
amount
cantidad
more than decent
más que decente
let me despite the fact that people know
déjame a pesar de que la gente sabe
who he is does not end up working and that
quién es no termina de funcionar y eso
is all
es todo
in my case because there is in Javier
en mi caso porque existe en javier
Canijo this last channel for  for me it is not
canijo este último canal para mí no es
something to see but to listen
algo para ver sino para escuchar
while I water I do chores with games in the
mientras riego hago tareas con juego al
sun, that is to say I learn some things
sol es decir me entero de algunas cosas
but it does not require me to pay attention, this
pero no requiere me aten es que este
channel was the best idea in the world so well I
canal fue la mejor idea del mundo con lo
put that in the background and that's it,
cual pues eso lo pongo de fondo y listo
however in Javier's videos
sin embargo en los vídeos de javier
I dance or put my ear to watch
bailarte o que poner oreja a mirar las
things and if the topics do not interest me they are
cosas y si los temas no me interesan son
videos that I am not going to consume no matter how
vídeos que no voy a consumir por muy
well made or structured they are,
bien hechos o estructurados que estén
not to mention that many times what appears
sin contar que muchas veces lo que sale
in those videos is already something that I have
en esos vídeos ya es algo que he
heard on his other channel, so
escuchado en su otro canal por lo cual
look before with less interest I am even going to have to
pues mira antes con menos interés aún
improve themes it affects
voy a tener que mejorar temáticas afecta
cell phones
a los celulares
and it is not
y no sea
content for my taste it is always
de contenido para mi gusto siempre es
good but being honest with myself I
bien pero siendo honesta conmigo mismo
prefer that each channel has its theme
prefiero que cada canal tenga su tema
but I do not know it is contradictory that you flip out
pero no sé es contradictorio que flipas
and more when you see my channel that one day it
y más cuando os veis mi canal que un día
plays games in front of others it is a story
hace juegos ante otros es un cuento está
everything is tomorrow a sheep in fact I remember
todo mañana un ovejas de hecho recuerdo
a comment in one of these videos that
un comentario en uno de estos vídeos que
follows very good video I think I want but
sigue muy buen vídeo yo creo quiera pero
because there was not more of that style
que porque no había más de ese estilo
obviously I will put comments if
obviamente os pondré comentarios si
I found but I would swear provi being in
encontrara pero juraría provi estando en
the town and now  same well look what it is
el pueblo y ahora mismo pues mira que es
that I can't find regular all white
que no encuentro regular a todo blanco
a chicken memory or is chicken hallucination
un pollo memoria o es pollo alucinación
in any case it's something that even
en cualquier caso es algo que incluso a
happens to me when antennas wake up
mí me pasa cuando antenas de despertador
my interest and I don't see all of their videos and
mi interés y no ver todos sus vídeos y
when I finish them like so
cuando se me terminan como
normally I leave
así que normalmente dejo deberes de
war homework for months until I can have
guerra durante meses hasta que pueda
many welcome back in
haber muchos bienvenidos de nuevo en
other words the permanence of chick
otras palabras la permanencia de pollito
in something seems like quite an achievement the truth
en algo parece todo un logro la verdad
but then if this happens to me I assume
pero luego si a mí me ocurre esto asumo
that there are other people to whom it
que hay otras personas a las que les
happens too therefore the
pasa también por lo tanto el denominador
common denominator that I come out is that if a channel
común que yo salgo es que si un canal no
is not working as it should it is due to a
está funcionando como debería es por una
matter of interest obviously youtube
cuestión de interés obviamente youtube
has errors that could be improved in
tiene errores que podrían mejorar en
2000 more factors that can help
2000 factores más que pueden ayudar a
the channel continue to take off trio 20
que el canal siga despegando trío 20 a
through the win but for my taste
través de la gana pero para mi gusto el
interest is a key in javi's case
interés es una clave en el caso de javi
the channel of javier del son ended I'm
terminó el canal de javier del hijo yo
sorry do you think I'm not going to consume
lo siento crees que no voy a consumir
javier beirán and like me now another where
javier beirán y como yo ahora otra donde
the people who have that happens but do more
la gente que le ocurra eso pero hace más
with the rest of the channels that have see the
con el resto de canales que tiene ver lo
same different thing on youtube is viable
mismo diferente en youtube es viable
because  different ways of telling it
porque diferentes formas de contarlo
different opinions of whatever
diferentes opiniones de lo que sea
etcetera etcetera but seeing the same thing three times right
etcétera etcétera pero ver tres veces lo
now I'm
mismo ahora mismo
sorry but in my case certainly
lo siento pero yo en mi caso desde luego
not obviously I can
que no obviamente esto lo puedo
exemplify this better with video games
ejemplificar mejor con los videojuegos
you have a doubt and it's a
tenéis duda y es un juego de zombies
super cool zombie game it gets better every day this is
superchulo mejora cada día esto es
our promotion it's fun and all the
nuestra promoción es divertido y toda la
fishing but after a few hours of playing
pesca pero pasadas unas horas de juego
let's say about two hundred well look I get
pongamos unas doscientas pues mira me
tired I leave it and when they put up
canso lo dejo y cuando vuelven a poner
new stuff dirty crow and really
cosas nuevas cuervo guarro y con
want to because he's back he
muchísimas ganas porque tiene de nuevo
believes me however
me cree sin embargo
he doesn't need to do absolutely anything
él no necesita hacer absolutamente nada
just put up the qualifiers and well
solo poner las clasificatorias y bueno
I'm going to lose my life in that
yo voy a solita a perder mi vida en ese
hole alone
pozo
well what do you think do you all
bueno qué pensáis ustedes están de
agree or well or I'm leaving do you
acuerdo o bueno o me voy estáis de
agree I'm leaving
acuerdo me voy
[Music]
[Música]